<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Post on ZeekHuge (Zubeen Tolani)</title>
    <link>https://www.zeekhuge.me/categories/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Post on ZeekHuge (Zubeen Tolani)</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 17 Jul 2016 23:37:27 +0530</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://www.zeekhuge.me/categories/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>PTP - Programming The PRUs 2: Docs, Commands and Tools</title>
      <link>https://www.zeekhuge.me/post/ptp_docs_commands_and_tools/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Jul 2016 23:37:27 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.zeekhuge.me/post/ptp_docs_commands_and_tools/</guid>
      <description>picture credits : xkcd.com
Preface: If the content here seems to be out of context, you&amp;rsquo;ll probably want to start from here.
So you have decided to play with PRUs and after this blinky post, you have some understanding about how to work with PRUs. Cool ! Thats a courageous decision, as PRUs are quite challenging. To make life easier, we need some tools to work along. This post will help you make some of your own tools, using mostly bash scripts/aliases, and explain how to use other known tools with PRUs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PTP - Programming The PRUs 1: Blinky</title>
      <link>https://www.zeekhuge.me/post/ptp_blinky/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Jul 2016 15:45:08 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.zeekhuge.me/post/ptp_blinky/</guid>
      <description>This is the first post in a series of posts that will try to put the PRU programming process in the simplest and the most logical form, connecting all the dots (rpmsg, remoteproc etc). The posts of this series will have PTP (Programming The Pru) at the beginning of its title. As its just the beginning, this post aims to get you a blinky application using PRUs on your BeagleBone Black.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Some Shots</title>
      <link>https://www.zeekhuge.me/post/some_shots/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Jul 2016 03:00:17 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.zeekhuge.me/post/some_shots/</guid>
      <description> BeagleScope project can be found here
Some Shots These are are some clicks of the hardware setup that I am going to use for the beaglescope project.
 Pic 1 : BBB power supply    Pic 2 : ADC power connections    Pic 3 : ADC power source     Pic 4 : Something like a cape     Pic 5 : The connections of &amp;#39;something like a cape&amp;#39;    Pic 6 : ADC data connectors    Pic 7 : Connection with the ADC connectors    Pic 8 : Just everything all together   </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A handful of commands and scripts to get started with BeagleBone Black</title>
      <link>https://www.zeekhuge.me/post/a_handfull_of_commands_and_scripts_to_get_started_with_beagleboneblack/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Jun 2016 19:56:39 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.zeekhuge.me/post/a_handfull_of_commands_and_scripts_to_get_started_with_beagleboneblack/</guid>
      <description>Here I have compiled a list of commands and some info to get you started with BeagleBone Black. I will keep updating this list of commands as I find something new . I hope that it will save you some time .
picture credits: xkcd.com
All of these commands are to be executed on the BeagleBone black (BBB for short) itself after you login as root, and are expected to work on kernel version 4.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Working with PRUs @BeagleBoneBlack : Introduction to PRUs</title>
      <link>https://www.zeekhuge.me/post/working_with_prus_beagleboneblack_introduction_to_prus/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Jun 2016 14:27:03 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.zeekhuge.me/post/working_with_prus_beagleboneblack_introduction_to_prus/</guid>
      <description>This is the first in a series of posts to explain and provide with some basic examples to work on PRU cores in AM335x. The AM335x SoC can be found on famous embedded board BeagleBone Black. The post are:
 Introduction to PRUs (this) To make you comfortable with the concept of realtime systems with PRUs, and basic introduction to various peripherals in the PRU-ICSS subsystem.
 Remoteproc To explain the working of remoteproc Linux driver to manipulate remote processing unit ie PRU for AM335x SoC.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>